Manchester Evening Herald Photograph Collection
Vernon Historical Society
- Inventory
  - Vernon El puppet show-Vernon, 4/14/1980; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.847)
  - Fishing Derby-Vernon, 4/21/1980; Topics: Recreation (Box 6, Folder MH.848)
  - Suburban Women's Club Clown Town-Vernon, 4/29/1980; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 6, Folder MH.849)
  - Highway work-Vernon Circle-Vernon, 05/??/80; Topics: Transportation; Vernon Circle (Box 6, Folder MH.850)
  - Marie Herbst, Robert Hurd, Ardis Abbott of Historical Society-Vernon, 05/??/80; Names: Herbst, Hurd, Abbott| Topics: Vernon Center; Landmarks (Box 6, Folder MH.851)
  - St. Joseph's Church-Rockville, 05/??/80; Topics: Churches (Box 6, Folder MH.852)
  - Kindergarden screening-Northeast School-Rockville, 05/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.853)
  - Sykes School-Stage Curtain-Rockville, 05/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.854)
  - Marie Herbst-Mayor- & Tony Kalkus-Vernon, 05/??/80; Names: Herbst & Kalkus (Box 6, Folder MH.855)
  - William Kirby, Rockville Hospital Relations-Rockville, 05/??/80; Names: William Kirby| Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 6, Folder MH.856)
  - Colonial Crafts at Center Road School-Vernon, 5/3/1980; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.857)
  - Northeast School PTO Ice Cream Festival-Rockville, 5/5/1980; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.858)
  - John R. Cratty-Pres., Neiss, Inc.-Rockville, 5/7/1980; Names: John R. Cratty| Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.859)
  - RHS Valedictorian & Saludetorian-Rockville, 5/8/1980; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.860)
  - RHG Gift Shop opens-Rockville, 5/13/1980; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 6, Folder MH.861)
  - Capping Ceremonies for Hospital Volunteers-Rockville, 5/19/1980; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 6, Folder MH.862)
  - 75 year old woman from Scotland visits for Granddaughter's Wedding, 5/21/1980; Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 6, Folder MH.863)
  - National Brands Tire-ad.-Vernon, 5/22/1980; Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.864)
  - Safety Town-Vernon, 06/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.865)
  - Fashion Show at Middle School-Vernon, 06/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.866)
  - Marie Herbst & Donald Maguda at Fire Dept Banquet-Vernon, 06/??/80; Names: Marie Herbst & Donald Maguda| Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 6, Folder MH. 867)
  - Mayor Marie Herbst & Sykes School students-Vernon, 06/??/80; Names: Marie Herbst| Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.868)
  - Exchange Club senior picnic-Vernon, 06/??/80; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 6, Folder MH 869)
  - Razing of Pritchard Building-Rockville, 06/??/80; Topics: Housing; Rockville Redevelopment; Landmarks (Box 6, Folder MH.870)
  - Sheltered Workshop-Vernon, 06/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.871)
  - Julie Lamb-Vernon, 06/??/80; Names: Julie Lamb (Box 6, Folder MH.872)
  - Highway map-Vernon, 06/??/80; Topics: Transportation (Box 6, Folder MH.873)
  - Sykes School Play-Rockville, 06/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.874)
  - RHS "Z" Club meeting-Rockville, 06/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.875)
  - Welles Village Flag-Talcottville, 06/??/80; Topics: Talcottville; Senior Citizens (Box 6, Folder MH.876)
  - RHS Graduation-Rockville, 06/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.877)
  - Kids at Rockville Library-Rockville, 06/??/80; Topics: Rockville Library (Box 6, Folder MH.878)
  - Chorale Planning with Marie Herbst and Herbert Chatzsky-Verrnon, 06/??/80; Names: Herbst & Chatzsky| Topics: Entertainment (Box 6, Folder MH.879)
  - Susan Breslau-Vernon, 07/??/80; Names: Susan Breslau (Box 6, Folder MH.880)
  - Bank robber-Richard Westover-appears in Court-Rockville, 7/17/1980; Names: Richard Westover| Topics: Police Dept.; Law and Lawyers (Box 6, Folder MH.881)
  - Rt 86 construction at Rt 83 intersection-Vernon, 7/18/1980; Topics: Transportation; Vernon Circle (Box 6, Folder MH.882)
  - Tolland County 4H Fair-Vernon, 08/??/80; Topics: Entertainment; Farming (Box 6, Folder MH.883)
  - St Joseph's Church Fair-Rockville, 08/??/80; Topics: Churches; Entertainment (Box 6, Folder MH.884)
  - Ed Jordan;s Carpets-Ad-Vernon, 08/??/80; Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.885)
  - Tri Town Paint-ad-Vernon, 8/6/1980; Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.886)
  - Activities in Henry Park-Kids make Pyramid-Rockville, 8/7/1980; Topics: Entertainment; Parks (Box 6, Folder MH.887)
  - Activities at Henry Park-Kids playing in sprayer-Rockville, 8/7/1980; Topics: Entertainment; Parks (Box 6, Folder MH.888)
  - Alice in Wonderland play-Vernon, 8/21/1980; Topics: Schools & Education; Entertainment (Box 6, Folder MH.889)
  - Dr. Peter Jarvis of RGH-Rockville, 09/??/80; Names: Dr. Peter Jarvis| Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 6, Folder MH.890)
  - View from Rockville Ctr Park-Rockville, 09/??/80; Topics: Parks; Landmarks (Box 6, Folder MH.891)
  - Jane Lamb, Republican Candidate-Vernon, 09/??/80; Names: Jane Lamb| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 6, Folder MH.892)
  - Horses with cut tails-Vernon, 8/13/1980; Topics: Farming (Box 6, Folder MH.893)
  - Horse on Risley's Res. Dam-Rockville, 9/13/1980; Topics: Farming (Box 6, Folder MH.894)
  - Rt 86 Construction-Vernon, 9/20/1980; Topics: Transportation (Box 6, Folder MH.895)
  - Hospital Follies-Rockville, 10/??/80; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Entertainment (Box 6, Folder MH.896)
  - Emergency drill at RGH-Rockville, 10/??/80; Topics: Fire Dept.; Rockville Hospital (Box 6, Folder MH.897)
  - Quilters at 1st Cong Church-Vernon, 10/??/80; Topics: Recreation; Social Organizations; Churches (Box 6, Folder MH.898)
  - Safety Group-Texas Conf.-Vernon, 10/??/80; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 6, Folder MH.899)
  - Cub Scouts and DAR-Vernon, 10/??/80; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 6, Folder MH.900)
  - Candidates-Vernon (For names see envelop)9 candidates, 10/??/80; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 6, Folder MH.901)
  - William Lee's 103rd Birthday-Vernon, 1/7/1980; Names: William Lee (Box 6, Folder MH.902)
  - John F. Perry-Vernon, 10/7/1980; Names: John F. Perry (Box 6, Folder MH.903)
  - Thomas J. Wolff-Vernon, 10/7/1980; Names: Thomas J. Wolff (Box 6, Folder MH.904)
  - Suburban Women's Club Fashion Show-Vernon, 10/31/1980; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 6, Folder MH.905)
  - Election night-Vernon, 11/??/80; Topics: Politics and Elections (Box 6, Folder MH.906)
  - Police Safety Sign-Vernon, 11/??/80; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 6, Folder MH.907)
  - Hang Glider testing-Vernon, 11/??/80; Topics: Recreation (Box 6, Folder MH.908)
  - Sheltered Workshop-Rockville, 11/??/80; Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.909)
  - Dr. Michael Sharon-Vernon, 11/??/80; Names: Dr.Michael Sharon (Box 6, Folder MH.910)
  - Lake Street School Xmas Tree-Vernon, 11/26/1980; Topics: Schools and Education; Holidays (Box 6, Folder MH.911)
  - Suburban Women's Club-Auction and mitten tree-Vernon, 12/??/80; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 6, Folder MH.912)
  - Suburban Women's Club Santa House-Vernon, 12/??/80; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 6, Folder MH.913)
  - Golden Age Club Christmas Party-Vernon, 12/??/80; Topics: Social Organizations; Entertainment; Senior Citizens; Holidays (Box 6, Folder MH.914)
  - Cong. Church Fair-Talcottville, 12/4/1980; Topics: Churches; Entertainment (Box 6, Folder MH.915)
  - Queen Anne's Closet-Ad-Vernon, 12/6/1980; Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.916)
  - Xmas shopper-Ad-Vernon, 12/11/1980; Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.917)
  - Vernon El School & Middle School Prom-Vernon, 12/23/1980; Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.918)
  - Xmas Baby leaving Hospital-Rockville, 12/24/1980; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Holidays (Box 6, Folder MH.919)
  - Flag presentation at Rockville Memorial Nursing Home-Rockville, 01/??/81; Topics: Senior Citizens (Box 6, Folder MH.920)
  - Town Council & Reps presentation to Jr. Miss Sandy Tyrol-Vernon, 01/??/81; Topics: Town Government (Box 6, Folder MH.921)
  - Middle School students write about hostages (Iran?), 01/??/81; Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.922)
  - Atty. Raymond Desmond-Vernon, 01/??/81; Names: Raymond Desmond| Topics: Law and Lawyers (Box 6, Folder MH.923)
  - PTO Council-The Bellinos (Claire & John), 01/??/81; Names: Claire & John Bollino| Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.924)
  - Vernon El Cultural Awareness Day-Vernon, 02/??/81; Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.925)
  - Dr. Herbert DiMeola of RGH-Rockville, 02/??/81; Names: Dr. Herbert DiMeola| Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 6, Folder MH.926)
  - Chinese New Year at Lake St School-Vernon, 02/??/81; Topics: Schools and Education; Holidays (Box 6, Folder MH.927)
  - Fire-Rockville, 2/10/1981; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 6, Folder MH.928)
  - I-86 construction-Talcottville, 2/11/1981; Topics: Transportation; Talcottville (Box 6, Folder MH.929)
  - Talcottville School Valentine's Party-Talcottville, 2/14/1981; Topics: Schools and Education; Talcottville; Holidays (Box 6, Folder MH.930)
  - Maple Street School playground equip-Rockville, 03/??/81; Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.931)
  - Posters in office of Middle School-Vernon, 3/9/1981; Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.932)
  - Check presentation at Middle School-Vernon, 3/9/1981; Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.933)
  - Two girls with national gov. awards at Middle School-Vernon, 3/9/1981; Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.934)
  - Andrew Maneggia-Vernon, 5/4/1981; Names: Andrew Maneggia| Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.935)
  - John F. Perry Benefit Plans, Inc., 06/??/81; Names: John F. Perry| Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.936)
  - Vo-Ag Awards-Rockville, 6/5/1981; Topics: Schools and Education; RHS; Farming (Box 6, Folder MH.937)
  - Rob Cronmiller, Rev.-Vernon, 07/??/81; Names: Rob Cronmiller| Topics: Churches (Box 6, Folder MH.938)
  - Bernie Bentley, banjo man-Vernon, 7/23/1981; Names: Bernie Bentley| Topics: Entertainment (Box 6, Folder MH.939)
  - Jack Perry-Vernon, 01/??/82; Names: Jack Perry (Box 6, Folder MH.940)
  - Vernon Chorale-Vernon, 1/29/1982; Topics: Social Organizations; Entertainment (Box 6, Folder MH.941)
  - Casa Nova Restaurant-interior-Vernon, 2/2/1982; Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.942)
  - Corey R. Barton, murder suspect-Vernon, 4/26/1983; Names: Corey Barton| Topics: Police Dept.; Law and Lawyers (Box 6, Folder MH.943)
  - Fire at Apollo Plastics-Rockville, 7/7/1983; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 6, Folder MH.944)
  - Jack Perry-Vernon, 12/??/84; Names: Jack Perry (Box 6, Folder MH.945)
  - Rockville downtown from High Rise-Rockvliie, 2/22/1986; Topics: Landmarks (Box 6, Folder MH.946)
  - Adult Education-Vernon, 5/12/1986; Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.947)
  - Fire-Rockville, 6/6/1986; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 6, Folder MH.948)
  - Shops at Rt 30-Vernon, ??/??/87; Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.949)
  - Small Appliance Repair-Vernon, 8/8/1987; Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.950)
  - Diamond Showcase-Jim Keeshan-Vernon, 10/??/88; Names: Jim Keeshan| Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.951)
  - Casa Nova restaurant exterior-Vernon, 06/??/89; Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.952)
  - Neipsic Tennis Club-Vernon, 8/9/1989; Topics: Recreation; Social Organizations (Box 6, Folder MH.953)
  - St. Joseph's Church 60th Anniversary-Rockville, 6/23/1990; Topics: Entertainment; Holidays (Box 6, Folder MH.954)
  - Students from Middle School with Air Force Staff Sgt. Thomas W. Finnegan-Vernon, 5/10/1991; Names: Thomas W. Finnegan| Topics: Schools and Education (Box 6, Folder MH.955)